You
Thank you very much ladies and gentlemen right now I got to tell you about
The fabulous most groovy
Oh
Yeah, I'll have a four black coffee's media name baby baby baby baby
Shake
What's this deal baby full cut same as everyone doc, I mean he retarded
Retarded means slow was he slow no, you don't sound the retarded to me
He's a good kid and devil behind the wheel what the hell else more do you need to know so you don't think that there's something wrong with him
It's not saying anything there's nothing wrong with a little quiet. I know why they call him baby, right?
Wait, not his first words
So you're a mute baby is that what it is
Are you a mute no
So what are you listening to?
That's right you tell him baby
For God's sake scruff leave the kid alone you can't just be in crime right not without being a little criminal
I just want to find out what's going on between those ears decide of course from
Egyptian reggae
Just think that he thinks he's better than us
Once you sit there in his car keep his white shirt clean while the rest of us we roll in the dirt
One of these days baby you're gonna get blood on your hands and you're gonna find out that that shit don't wash off in the fucking sink
Relax the kid did his job. All right. I ever say that the kid wasn't great at his job. Nah, I think he's a star
What I've asked for him if he wasn't
Got a hint you told him pole either hardest nails or scared shit
You think about that baby mommy and daddy are getting in on enough where you get off
Here okay folks if you don't see me again, it's cuz I'm dead
Tell me about tonight buddy tonight darling
We'll have post heist revelry back in the area
That is the finest one and a dining of all the wines and dimes in town
Well, sir expect the lady and myself to darken your door once the nosebag is empty
The baby you did good kid. It'll be favorite next time Doc calls
Don't pick up
Don't listen to him
I
Now I get absolutely no pleasure in taking candy from baby, but we're fast approaching the day and you
Will be all paid up
One more job and I'm done one more job and we're straight sound good. Oh
Oh, I was gonna wait until we were square, but what the hell these are for you
Now give me your burner
I'm gonna need you behind the wheel again real soon you call them there
The woman came into the bank branch cloud and black business clothing
Oh
Sorry couldn't hear a banana my ear
I'm working today
You are so beautiful
They grow up so freaking fast, don't they
That is more important than our friendship
That's it working out for you and still the bull stands bloody but unrelenting
Gaston is running out of time. He's had his tries from horseback now. He must try to end this on foot
Retard him in slow. Was he slow?
No, was he slow?
No
Retard him in slow. Was he slow?
No, slow slow slow
Oh
I really don't wanna help you live.
B-A-B-Y, baby.
Whenever the sun don't shine.
So, where can I get you this fine morning?
Oh, don't worry if you need a second.
I have all the time in the world.
Are you recording this?
No, I...
Hello, testing.
What can I get you this fine morning, sir?
Oh, that's a kid's menu, right?
So you're just starting your day, or did you just get off?
I don't know if I ever get off. They call I go, you know.
So what is it you do?
I'm a driver. Oh, like a chauffeur?
You drive around important people? I guess I do. Anyone I'd know?
I hope not. Well, aren't you mysterious?
Maybe. Maybe?
This is the last time you hit the road just for fun.
I'm jealous. Sometimes all I wanna do is head west on 20 in a car I can't afford with a plan I don't have.
Just me, my music, and the road.
I'd like that, too.
So, you deciding anything yet? You are so beautiful.
You just decided that. Oh, well, thank you.
I'm sure you don't mean it. I do mean it.
Jonathan? Oh, sorry. You know, this isn't my badge.
I've only just started here. Is it Jonathan?
Yeah, that's a Jonathan. Well, if you have any more questions, just holler.
B-A-B-Y, baby.
I have a question. What's that song you're singing?
What's that song you're singing?
I don't know.
Baby, oh baby
I love to call you baby
I love for you to call me baby
When you squeeze me real tight
You make wrong things right
And I can't stop loving you
And I won't stop calling you baby
Baby, oh baby
You look so good to me baby
Oh, there you are.
I've been calling, baby. You have? I have.
My chicken just laid a very big egg. You in?
Am I in? It was a rhetorical question, baby.
You're in. I'll be there.
Music
Meet your new crew. Over here is Eddie No-Nose,
formerly Eddie the Nose. Well, what happened?
Don't ask me that. That's a No-Nose, No-No, Page One.
And right here is JD. He put the Asian in Home Invasion. And over there is the one and the only. Bats!
No need for intro, Doc. Everybody from the jungle to the trap. No bass.
She bored, right?
This one, he say listen to the music all the time.
The drive is supposed to be the eyes and the ears. Not just the eyes.
Why does he listen to music all the time, Doc? It's got mental problems.
I'm the one got the mental problems in the crew.
Position taken. He's got tinnitus. Tinnitus?
He had an accident when he was a kid. He still got a hum on the drum. Play his music to drown it out.
Yeah, but you're filming.
Hat.
Huh? Your tattoo says hat?
Yeah. They used to say hate. But then crew's my chances of employment.
They got the year removed. How's that working out for you?
Who doesn't like hats? So, Doc, how many jobs done with the kid?
If you can't take my word for him, then get back in that fucking elevator.
You never heard of the Spirit of 85?
The Joy Rider? Yeah. The ghost that baited cops
during 130 on 85. Headlights off, brake lights disconnected.
He drove them around at circles on Spaghetti Junction. Left him in the dust every
time. That was our boy there. Wasn't it like ten years ago? Yeah. Well, like I said, that was our boy.
He's been boosting cars since he was old enough to see over the dash. He stole my Mercedes.
Had a lot of merch in it. I watched him do it too. I didn't stop him though, because I was just
blinded by the balls on that kid. Of course, he didn't know who I was or the worth of
the junk in the trunk once he dumped it. But once I tracked him down, I made sure to tell
him who I was, what I was capable of, and how much he owed me.
Since he's been paying me back, he's also shown me what he's capable of. Wow.
I just drew a whole goddamn map and chalk while we've been standing here squawking.
That's pretty fucking impressive, right? Shop! Let's talk it!
Baby, you with us?
Let's talk it over.
What up?
I got a question, Doc.
Why would I believe phones over here to goddamn word you're saying? You lay down in your whole play.
He ain't even listening. Baby?
The target is an armored truck at perimeter trust in Dunwoody, 10 a.m. sharp. We have the details
of the route because someone at the depot has a nasal problem. The bank itself is right
near the Buford Highway, so we should be able to hit the ramp within 60 seconds again now. We also have
a diversion crew. They're going to blow up a bread truck a ways away, keep the fuzz busy.
The dress code is the Michael Myers Halloween mask, but don't all buy your mask at the same time.
It looks suspicious. The switch car is ready, but you want me to hit the long
stay parking structure at Heartsfield Jackson to get a high speed vehicle that stays colder longer.
Boost the commuter car, family car, something that blends in well with morning traffic.
Something on the heavy side in case we need to ram the cops off the road.
We need to escalate, Yukon, Avalanche, whatever. We need to be ready for an 830 start.
In the a.m. Questions?
Well, ain't y'all cute? That's my baby.
Fuck your baby.
What's in there is ours.
It belongs to us.
They took our money, our hard-earned paper.
They snuck in when we were asleep last night and took the parents off the chair and emptied our
wards. They got what's rightfully ours.
Let's go get it back. What's rightfully ours.
What the fuck is this, man?
Austin Powers.
Doc said Michael Myers. This is Mike Myers. It should be the Halloween mask.
This is a Halloween mask. No, the killer dude from Halloween.
All you mean, Jason? No!
Let's go. Wait, wait, wait. I gotta start the song over.
What the fuck?
Okay, go.
Let's go.
We out. Let's go.
Go.
Come on, get him.
What the fuck? We got a hero.
Get him.
Do your job, baby. Let's go.
Shit.
Watch out. Watch out.
Watch out.
Get him.
Yeah!
That's how you do it, baby.
Come on.
Yeah.
What the fuck? Soldier boy.
He ain't giving up, huh?
Come on, Soldier boy.
Shit! No, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
Got your ass now.
Get him.
Hey, damn that, G.I. Joe mother fucking dead right?
Got him.
New ride, let's go.
Come on boys, let's rock. Move, move, move, move.
Huh, sweetheart? Oh my god.
Get out the car! I don't have a child!
I got one too. Get the fuck out.
Come on. Get in.
Bring your sorry ass home.
Get your dead real ass over here.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, let's rock.
Let's go.
Oh shit. No.
Fuck!
I left my shotgun behind. What? I left my shotgun behind.
Not groovy, J.D. Not groovy at all.
Come on, come on, come on.
Get out.
Get out!
All units be on the lookout for a red, Saturn,
aura, license plate, and number.
and try to fight him up.
This is JD over there and that's Jamie's the idiot.
Tew Brach boys, though.
Saw that associate fight.
Come on, man.
You can tell me.
No.
You're a good driver.
You're a bad liar, though.
In this business, the moment you catch feelings,
there's a moment you catch a bullet.
Now pick up your purse and go get the coffee.
Come on, everybody!
Come on, man.
You can tell me.
Come on, everybody!
Hey!
All right.
Get it.
You move to the left.
Move to the right.
Got a damn time.
Get it.
Oh, you looking for JD?
International man of mystery?
Because he's long gone, baby.
Let's put it there.
We'll drink.
So, this is it.
I'm a man of my word.
And you're all straight, baby.
That's it?
Sure is.
You're all paid up.
Cost for celebration.
Yeah, sure is.
Oh, yeah, well, before you go completely crazy.
You need to sunset that ride.
Drive safe, baby.
I'm going to get out of here.
I'm leaving you tomorrow.
Seems to me girl, you know I've done all I can.
You see your big stone and I bow.
I'm easy like Sunday morning.
You're back!
I sure am.
Then you sir are going to be my very last customer
because I am walking out that door
Can I come with you?
You don't have work or nothing?
Uh, I don't.
I, um, don't move work.
Wow, you seem real happy about that.
Yeah, sure am.
I don't blame you.
Well, you're welcome to come with,
but I don't know how excited you're going to find the laundromat.
I gotta run some errands.
Oh.
But think about what you want, and I will stick around just for you.
Coffee?
Please. Yeah, cream of sugar.
So, how are you two getting along?
Oh, good.
He's sweet, isn't he?
That kid?
He's been coming here since before me.
I think maybe his mom used to work here.
Huh.
Now what you want?
Your name?
Well, you can get that for free.
It's Debbie.
Deborah.
What song?
The Beck one? Yeah.
Bucks Up Time, D-E-B-O-R-A, and I think that's just D-E-B-R-A.
I don't know that one.
Oh, it goes, um...
I bet you, Jaycee Penny,
I think your name type is
Jenny.
Jenny?
The song's about him wanting to get with Jenny
and her sister to whose name is Deborah.
So it's not even really about me.
It's about the sister.
My sister's name is Mary.
She has got all the songs.
Mary, Mary, where are you going to?
Proud Mary, keep on burning.
The wind cries, Mary.
She's got me beat again.
She's got endless songs.
I got one.
You got two.
That's the other one.
Deborah, the song I'm talking about.
Who, by? Trex.
I've heard of them, but don't know that one.
How's it go?
Oh, Deborah.
Always look like a zebra.
A zebra?
A gazibra, I guess.
I'm working back and right, so you can call me D-B-R-A.
I think I actually got Deborah on here.
What? How many of those do you have?
I got different iPods for different days and moods.
Oh, and you're in a...
pink and glittery mood.
I am now.
What is your name?
Baby.
Wait, what? Your name's Baby.
B-A-B-Y Baby.
Yeah?
Then you have us all beat.
Every damn song is about you.
We could drive back and forth across the states forever
and never run out of baby songs.
We might run out of cast.
Did your mom call you Baby as a kid?
Sometimes.
She used to work here?
Sometimes, but, uh...
she was a singer, too.
What does she do now?
Nothing.
Uh, I could find Deborah if she wanted.
Debbie!
Crying out loud.
I play it for me sometimes.
I don't have to get out of here.
Deal?
Yeah, deal.
Now you know what you want yet?
To get out of here.
You're right.
I do like it.
So,
what's your story, Baby?
You from here?
I am.
I'm from here.
Keep going. Keep going.
You're from here.
You're a driver.
You like music.
You don't talk much.
No. I've, uh...
spoken more to you today
than I have to anyone all year.
Whoa! Okay.
Not a motormouth.
Noted.
Yeah, yeah.
I have this hearing thing.
I was in an accident when I was little.
Is that what happened to your mom?
Yeah. Yeah, my dad.
I miss her.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be. I live with my foster dad,
but now he's getting old,
so it's more like I'm looking after him.
Yeah, I know how that feels.
I have to look after my mom
when she got sick.
It might seem tough now,
but once they're gone,
therefore,
I don't have much to keep me here anymore.
You don't?
You know,
we could get together some other time.
Some other place.
Oh, you mean, uh,
somewhere that's not a diner or a laundromat?
Yeah, well, it's not that this isn't nice, but...
Well, we could go to, uh...
Um,
oh, Bacchanalia.
I've never been.
I hear it's nice.
Oh, it's the finest wine
in the dining of all the wines in Dyson Town.
That is nice.
Um, they got me pulling devils this week, though.
What about next week?
What's your schedule like?
I don't know. Oh, I forgot.
They call you go.
No, I mean, I'm not working.
You're not driving anymore?
No. I'm sorry.
No, don't be. It's my choice.
Well, aren't you the lucky one?
You took that?
I saw these guys go marching
in the banquet hallway mass.
Weapons strong.
They were tech.
Pizza?
Whoa.
That was that?
I know.
Pizza!
Woo-hoo!
Hello.
You're all good,
a gentleman picked this up already.
A gentleman?
Who was it?
He was not on the show.
He's not on the show.
I don't know.
He's on the show.
You're all good.
A gentleman picked this up already.
Who is that?
It's my old boss.
Uh...
Excuse me. One second.
Thank you, baby.
Have a good night.
Good meal, baby.
That foie gras terrain is something, huh?
Yeah.
You don't look happy to see me. Why?
I said we were straight, but did you think we were done?
But that was it.
I'm sorry.
I guess I did.
Well, I could give you the good news and the bad news,
except there is no bad news.
The good news is you're about to make a lot of money.
And the good news is you're about to make a lot of money.
I got a job, Doc.
Yeah.
The white slave away delivering good fella's pizzas
just to afford a night out here.
When you could make all that dough with a great fella,
me,
and then take your gal here for fucking dinner
every night of the week.
You paid all that money.
You've been doing dinner every night of the week.
You paid off your debt. Now it's time to profit.
This is the fun bit, baby.
By the time this job is over, you'll be rolling the money
by Maserati's and feeding your gal catfish dipped in gold.
So what do you say? Are you in?
Oh, yeah.
Am I in?
No, don't answer my question with another question.
You give me one or two replies, yes or no?
No, Doc.
You know I never do a job with the exact same crew twice, right?
Yes.
And you also know you've been my driver for every job since we met.
So I'm of the thinking
that you are my lucky charm
and that I'm not doing this job without you.
Now, I don't think I need to give you this feature
of what happens when you say no, how I can break your legs
and kill everyone you love, because you already know that, don't you?
Yeah.
So what's it gonna be?
A wheeler and a wheelchair.
The first one?
I'll pick you up in the morning.
Don't stay out too late now.
Oh, and your, uh,
waitress girlfriend, she's cute.
Let's keep it that way.
Good night, sir.
Well,
there was some pretty fine wine in and dining.
I must have friends in high places to get a table there.
I don't know about that.
Is everything okay, baby?
Yeah, it will be.
You wanna talk about it?
I'm making me a cup of coffee.
I mean, I don't.
I make terrible coffee.
I want to, but I...
I can't right now.
You know, Yuki,
you don't have to worry about me.
You can tell me anything.
I'm not worried about you.
I mean, I...
You're the best thing that's happened to me in a long time.
And I just...
worry that...
I'm not good enough for you.
Well...
don't.
I can see you're kind in your...
desert.
Desert.
And I'm here for you when you're ready.
What do you know tomorrow?
Will you tell me?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Morning.
These places never get rolled.
People don't realize that there's gold in them, their hills,
and those that do don't have the stones to pull off a job so public in the hub of it.
This place will be ripe around this time tomorrow,
but I need to do something for me today.
I can't be seen in there, but you can.
So go inside, take note of the number of cameras and positions,
the number of registers open,
the number of employees and the number of customers.
Because they're a guard, because he armed with a he banded glass.
And get in line by some stamps.
Take your buds out, pull your shades off.
I'll end up taking a few of us suspicious.
I'll be right back.
No banded glass, but I'm a guard.
Done cameras, eight registers to open all of our customers and full employees.
Thank you.
Uh, stamps?
Is that your boy?
Sure. Yeah, he sure is.
How old is he?
Four.
Eight.
They grow up so freaking fast, don't they?
Does he have a name?
You have a name, don't you?
Sam.
Well, Sam, I got a mint with your name on it.
You have a mint that says Sam?
Oh, sweet.
Are you here tomorrow?
Sure am, working nine to five, just like Dolly.
Dolly Parton.
I like her.
Who doesn't? Everybody wants happiness, nobody wants pain.
But you can't have a rainbow without a little rain.
Why is Lady?
Yeah, she sure is.
Bye.
Hit me.
No banded glass, one armed guard.
Ten cameras, eight registers, three open.
And, uh, eleven customers.
Four employees.
Anything else?
The teller seemed nice.
She gave me a mint.
Did she?
Yeah, he probably wouldn't even need to use a gun with her.
Just say boo and she'll give you the big bills first.
Chips off the old block.
I'll show you.
What floor are you on?
Third.
Those stairs must be a real bitch for Joe, huh?
It's my business to know everything.
So, are they a bitch?
It's an elevator.
Ooh, fancy.
So,
are you gonna see tonight?
Yes, you will.
You're not just saying what you think I want to hear, right?
You consider me a friend, don't you?
You and I are a team.
Nothing's more important than our friendship.
Good to know.
You'll be out of this shit hole soon.
You're going up in the world.
Bo's Donner, what do you have?
Is Debra there?
Debbie, phone.
Keep it short.
Hi.
It's Baby.
Hey.
What do I owe this Donner?
I just wanted to hear your voice.
Am I still seeing you later?
I have to drive again.
Oh, okay.
I thought you all were done with that.
So did I.
Just know what I want.
And what do you want, Baby?
I want us to head west on 20.
In a car we can't afford.
With a plane we don't have.
Keep driving and never stop.
Are you serious?
I am Debra.
You in?
I'm in, Baby.
See you soon.
I'm in.
Holy Calamity!
Scream insanity!
You ever going to be another great fan of me?
Baby!
There he is.
Hey, Baby.
You hear no evil's back, huh?
Have you seen this kid move?
Yeah, I think.
I think Doc likes having him around because he can park in a disabled spot.
Disabled spot?
Yeah, he got some shit wrong with his ears.
Tonight I saw something.
Anyway, he got to listen to music 24 hours a day to drown it in the wine and his ears.
Oh, shit!
You know who else has the exact same thing and does it exact same thing?
Barbra Streisand.
Do you look like I know a fucking thing about Barbara Streisand?
Hey, watch your mouth.
It's the lady you're talking to.
Yeah.
Watch your mouth.
I'll watch what I want to watch.
Is that true?
Do you have music in your head all the time?
Drown up the noise?
Yeah.
It keeps me moving.
It's an escape.
I get it.
Hey, buddy, you seen that violin?
I had a violin here.
Shut up!
I used to fool around with cars when I was a kid.
Grab around all night, look speed-freak, listen to the radio.
I used to have my special tape.
They had my special tape.
They had my killer track on it.
Get me flying.
You got one of those?
Sure.
What is it?
Riding Rock.
What? Queen?
Yeah, it's got that crazy big guitar solo.
That's how my brother used to play.
Sheer heart attack right through the wall.
You got it on here?
I got it on this one.
Play it.
Let's do that killer track.
Yeah.
What you ladies listening to?
Queen.
Strikes saying now, queen, the fuck, what y'all gonna do?
Y'all gonna belt out show tunes on the way to the job?
You don't need a score for a score.
You just boom, boom,
you're gonna put your foot on the gas
and drive a goddamn car.
That's all the music you need, folks.
Come on now.
You never been a wheel man?
You never had a lucky song?
Well, cigarette song, opera heist,
glass of scotch,
absolutely, but not before a job.
I got enough demons right here
playing music all the time.
Yeah, well, that I believe.
Had a buddy once walk away from a job.
You know why? Because something was playing
and we about to go in, he won't get out the fucking car.
Why?
Because knock knock knock on Heather's door,
he was playing on the FM.
Called it a heck song.
That ended the role by boys and men,
Hotel California by the Eagles.
He called them all heck songs.
Then come talking about some crazy shit like,
we all gonna die.
So what, you bail on the job?
Fuck no, I didn't bail on the job.
I wasn't got that money.
And we ain't die either.
Do all your stories end up with somebody dying?
Guess you just gotta fire down, huh?
I need four pairs of eyes
and three sets of ears, gather up.
The postal service is dying.
People don't care about their mail anymore.
Lucky for us.
Their loss is our gain.
Money orders.
For I happen to know a guy who has a machine
that can turn blank ones into green.
Each box contains 250 slips per box.
Each slip worth up to a grand,
that's quarter of a mil per box.
Dot dot dot, you do the math.
Darling goes in the front.
Buddy takes a five alligator count
and follows her inside.
You put on these privacy glasses.
Blind, the CCTV camera.
Another five alligator count.
Darling gets in line.
Buddy takes her hostage.
Shotgun to her head.
That gets you guys in the back office.
We real play that a lot.
Uh-huh.
Baby drives bats around the loading dock.
Bats uses this security card,
supplied by an insider with a nasal problem,
to get in the staff entrance and cover the rear.
You guys grab all the boxes
and get back to baby and the waiting car.
Did you get all that, baby?
Yeah.
Okay, one more thing.
We need some fresh hardware.
Not traceable to us or any previous jobs.
Now I've got some contacts that get us some clean firepower.
So the pickup is tonight.
But after the pickup, you come straight back here.
You all have an early start in the morning
and there's eyes everywhere.
So you're staying the night here.
We're gonna get together now.
MUSIC
Pull over there. I gotta take a leak.
Want some gum?
Want some gum, buddy?
Yeah, I'll take some gum.
Tell me what we're gonna do with all that money.
We're gonna go to Vegas.
We'll put it all on red.
We'll get married again.
And it'll be real romantic.
You know, it was real, real romantic.
It was real, real romantic.
We need to have that guy.
Which guy? The guy that robbed you?
The guy that called you a whore?
The guy that looked at you funny?
The last one.
Yeah, I do remember that.
Bats just looked at me funny.
You already killed bats?
Not before the job, silly.
Do you think we should talk about this in front of baby?
He won't say a thing.
Will you, baby?
Jesus Christ.
What did you steal all this?
Said you want some gum.
Fuck I'm supposed to do the pay for it.
Let's go.
Looks like the farmer's market is open.
Farmer's market?
Yeah, Doc says we gotta go see the butcher.
Come on, you're going in with us.
We might not be leaving in this.
And, uh, find some funky on there.
Just in case we gotta rip this joint up.
Take this.
Act like you know how to use it.
Why would he need it?
We gotta swagger it like you got one.
So we don't all look like a bunch of pussy.
We're just gonna leave it.
We're gonna leave it.
What's with the earbuds?
Recordness or something?
It's just his music.
Yeah, he's loony. He's just like his tunes.
What's he listening to?
I got no.
Come on, let me check.
Tequila!
Which reminds me, why did Mexican do
throw his wife off the cliff?
Oh, you're still alive, right?
Uh-huh. Then I guess we ain't ever met.
Shut the fuck up!
I've got it.
Vuelas!
Welcome to La Chacaparri.
Tonight, gentlemen, madame,
we have only the finest cuts of pork
direct from the local smokehouse.
You're all experienced butchers yourself.
I assume you are aware that the humble pig
can be cooked from nose to tail,
everything but the squeal.
I can offer you nine cuts
at the best prices in all of Christendom.
So, let's dive in headfirst.
From the jowl comes the God-sent Roman bacon
that is Juan Chiale.
From the shoulder of the hog comes the
bosted but a tough but tasty cut.
The picnic shoulder is a favorite of those
who enjoy the smoking of pigs.
The center cut loin, the double cut pork chops,
baby back ribs, and the serrano ham.
On the back leg, of course.
All delicious.
And, of course, we have a fine selection of sausages.
Well, I'm hungry.
Fantastic.
And your choice is?
Well, I'm gonna go with the picnic shoulder
because I just love smoking pigs.
BAM!
Dundee.
Dumb son of a bitch.
Whoa!
Fuck, bats! You got my wife shot! I don't like that!
Relax, buddy. You handled it.
What the fuck, you piece of shit?
You shot the gun-tomans. Weren't they fucking Doc's contacts?
They were Doc's contacts.
Guess what? They were pigs. Look at the boxes. It's APD.
I clocked that tall stripper baker
with that fake-ass Louis Vuitton hat right off the bat.
He busted me in 98.
Now, I don't know about you love birds, fucking without a condom,
but when somebody gets ready to barbecue me,
I'm gonna fool them in the best shit I've ever seen.
Get him!
Baby, don't let him get away.
Get us out of here, baby. Let's move.
Come on, let's go. Move.
Takeda.
Not that easy.
Whoo!
Bats are fucking crazy.
When you folks name your bats, you're gonna end up crazy.
I don't doubt you're crazy, but your real name is not bats.
So says you.
You think my real name's Darling?
Yeah, or Buddy? No, they're nicknames.
Codenames, monikers.
So what's your real name, Darling?
Monica.
I thought we were allowed to discuss names.
We're not.
Baby, what's your real name?
Huh?
Hey, stop, stop, stop up here.
Stop up here.
So stop, I'm hungry.
No.
Stop the car!
No? You telling me no?
I don't want to go in there.
I don't want to go in.
Well, hello, baby.
Buddy's at the floor back there, and you don't say shit.
Now all of a sudden, you getting...
you getting riled up about stopping at a dime?
I don't want to go in there. It sucks.
What about that recommendation?
We gots to go in there.
When something is wrong with my baby
Something's wrong with me
Now why else, old man?
You should be thinking old bads.
For being a walking fucking death wish.
You're gonna not treat all of my jobs like it's my last.
But what you do within this group affects all of us.
So don't care, boy. You're gonna get your money tomorrow.
Plus, uh, you guys got noses to feed.
Well, yeah, like you're Mr. Clean.
Mr. What-up-a-fuck-a-wombie.
Can I get you anything to drink?
Uh, yeah, I think it'd be a coke all around, right?
How you saying in your language? Coke-a?
So let me get three cokes and one...
Coca.
Four cokes?
Yeah.
Look here's the deal.
You robbed to support a drug habit.
I do drugs to support a robbery habit.
That's clever.
That's my job, see.
It's you two's on that case.
So you doubt our credentials?
Wall Street, right?
Doctor, I ain't done.
Don't you tell me shit?
Just an educated guess.
For my uneducated man.
Well, that's-I don't be fascinated to hear your thoughts on the matter.
Tell me from way off, buddy.
You were a star broker.
Maybe a different wife, maybe kids.
You stack your paper, but you say shit like,
work hard, play hard, or but you play a little too hard.
You rack up debt.
The type of debt that'll make a white man blush.
Maybe you get into a little trouble.
Maybe you get your hand caught in a corporate cookie jar.
Maybe you leave and run off to the desert.
Maybe with your favorite lap dancer in tow.
Maybe you disappear into a world consistent to three things.
Money, sex, drugs, and action.
Oh shit, that's full.
Am I close?
This is how I look at it.
You guys just think this is a trip.
Either way, if you are Wall Street,
you're a bigger fucking crook than I could ever be.
I'm gonna go right ahead and speak for the two of us.
I think you know us.
You don't.
You think you're the last word in crazy.
You're not.
And believe me, when I tell you,
you don't want to see my buddy mad.
You haven't seen how relentless he is.
Because when he sees red,
you will see nothing but black.
You hear that speed?
That's some Oscar shit right there.
That was nice. You rehearsed that?
You see the shit, baby?
See that? This is a prime example of a man
who loves a woman.
You guys perfectly do.
I mean that.
What can I get you to eat?
Get these cats some half of meals and I won't take care of them.
I won't take care of them.
Uh, Deborah.
My friend here, he doesn't like this place.
But I think he's telling us.
So let me ask you something, Deborah.
What's his problem?
And maybe your friend would like to fill out a suggestion slip.
Tell us how to improve our service.
Baby, you know that bitch?
No.
Okay.
That's bad.
I got this.
Let's put the fuck up your problem.
Hey.
Okay.
I'll make sure you tip the knife, lady.
If you will stay with me.
Yes.
Every little bit first.
Bananas.
Bananas is a code word.
Whenever a deal is done with one of my clients,
they call me on the phone and they say the word bananas
and then they hang up.
I did not hear the word bananas tonight.
So you tell me who died.
Well, you're not going to tell me who died.
I'm not going to tell you who died.
So you tell me who died.
Well, your contacts was cops, Doc.
I know.
They were my cops.
Yeah, well, they fired first.
And I'm not going to take a bullet for you
and nobody else in this motherfucker.
Is that true? They fired first?
Yep.
Baby?
I have somebody on the planet Earth.
I will ask whoever the fuck I want.
Go home, jobs off.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
We are 24 hours from being descended upon by this entire city.
Those pigs are in hog heaven.
The only way they can ID us is with a Ouija board or some shit.
Well, your name only takes four letters to spell out.
But that bad thing my real fucking name.
It's over, Leon.
Get out of town.
Well, well, I ain't running, Doc.
I said we'd drive into the storm.
Ride the hurricane.
We could be on a non-extradition beach,
drinking non-extradition cocktails,
counting our non-extradition cash in 23 hours.
And who do we get to fence those money orders
since you shot the fence?
Buddy got a guy.
I mean, I'm just taking a wild guess here,
but Buddy got a guy, ain't that right, Wall Street?
Yeah, I got a guy.
So let's fucking do this.
I only hear three voices,
and the last time I checked there's four in a car.
Baby, your call.
Time to make a big boy decision.
Did we do this thing or not?
He's out voting. We're doing it.
I said we all get some sleep.
Get ready for this fucking thing.
Baby, your call.
Time to make a big boy decision.
Do we do this thing or not?
I
Ready going baby
Coffee
That's two a.m.
That doesn't sound smart
You fucking kidding me. I got enough of my plate worried about bats. I got to worry about you too now
You know what do me a favor if you're gonna mail it in at the post office tomorrow
Then go on your little caffeine run
And they'll come back
If you're just in this for the buzz if driving is just some kind of escape for you then go
Child doing it
Just making sure everything's ready for tomorrow
We're like he's going somewhere two o'clock in the morning
I know
Good
Cuz we gotta discuss this
No, no, it's the same one
Baby your call time to make a big boy decision. Yeah, we did this thing or not. No, you want to go and do that
It's just me fooling around. I like to record stuff
Why you like to course though?
You the police
Supposed to grill on the road not the cops speak up, baby
I like to listen back to conversations. I think music out of the words song mixes just something I do
That's one fucking dumbass excuse
Be fair even the cops couldn't come up with an excuse said fucking dumbass now
Can you play us one of your mixes? I can't
They're home. Well, it's like we all go somewhere to clock in one
Come on
I'll live really far away
No, you don't
Wake up, baby time to explain
Joe what are you doing the cripple? Oh, don't worry about him
He's good
Ain't gonna
Watch play or something, baby
This is
Deborah isn't that the waitress from the diner
You say you didn't know that bitch
Why would you say you didn't know her? Have you been talking to Deborah about us? I don't say nothing about wheels
He can't say nothing. Yeah, but he can read motherfucking lips. Okay?
Take this fool back to his shithole. I'll find another driver for tomorrow. Doc. I'm a baby
Well, I can take more needs to go get him home safe. No, you're not getting a new driver. I've been on every job since we met I
Don't go to the cops. I screw on the road. Now. I'm not slow. I'm fast
I'm your driver tomorrow. I'm driving
Well, you heard the kid he's driving
This afternoon
Chance's got her thunderstorms throughout most of the day low tonight about point
Remember what's in there is ours belongs to us
They got our money they got our mama's jewels
So let's go back in there and take back what's ours
I
Boom boom boom. It's go time, baby. How the fuck I look
Oh
We gotta go we gotta go we gotta go
Put your fucking foot on the gas
Oh
What did you do, baby?
What the fuck did you do? I moved
Oh
Your fault
I
Egor flashing KIM
e
ouch
You know what I'm saying?
Get out of the car lady!
You get it!
Get out of here!
I need some gettin'
OH!
OH MY NEMESISSE
It looks like when Universal Thats' a hijab
I got the ball!
He's on, man.
What the fuck?
The police tell us that three robbers entered a US post office branch downtown shortly after 1 p.m.
But what started after the robbery?
Shit, Joe! Joe, Joe, Joe!
You alright? I'm so sorry, this is all my fault.
We gotta get out of here, alright? Thanks for back.
I know, I know, but I can't leave you here.
Bo's daughter, what do you have?
Is Debra there?
Debbie? She's with a customer right now, you want a hold?
Just tell her baby's coming.
Baby?
V-A-B-Y, baby.
We've got a look out for 1986 Purple, Chevy Caprice, and we're about to release Mellon's on the news.
Four policemen who have entered a downtown shootout
after police say they're in the police post and they're still at large are considered extremely dangerous.
Hello.
My name is Joseph.
I like TV.
And I also like to listen sometimes to old records through the vibrations.
I like frozen peas and meatloaf and white bread and peanut butter.
Spread to the edge.
Please look after me. Thank you.
Please look after me.
This is the Atlanta Police Department. All residents remain inside your homes.
There is an armed and dangerous criminal on the loose. Do not go outside until all players get to the police.
Hello.
Your buddy's here.
Good luck, Bertz. I was hoping I would catch you too.
And here you are.
Monica Castello.
Monica.
My darling.
She was a good girl.
I love...
I loved her.
What about Deborah, baby? Is she...
Is she a good girl? You love her?
Yes, I do.
That's too bad.
I love you.
This is the bathroom key.
Thanks.
That's plenty.
Thank you.
I'm never gonna quit.
With just being my stick.
I'm gonna stay right here with you.
As long as you're with her, baby.
I'm afraid you still have the face to music.
How are you two doing tonight?
We're doing just fine.
Ain't that right, baby?
Come on, come on.
You can't keep running, baby.
There's no escape.
Fuck, let's get out of here.
Fuck.
What's happening, baby?
I have to go.
No. I'm coming with you.
You just shot a guy.
Who? Him.
Atlanta Police Department. You on the ground.
Are you okay? Can you show me where you've been shot?
Yeah.
Right there.
Officer down.
Shot fired. I repeat, shot fired and boosed down here.
Unit 412, Carly on scene, requested backup.
Possible female hostage.
Who's this?
It's Baby.
Like I said, who's this?
I need your help.
I'm afraid this line is dead.
Baby, we need to get out of here.
I just need one thing first.
And then it's just us, music, and the road.
But we don't have a car or music.
Yeah, we do.
Get out.
Check out Bonnie and Clyde, yo.
Bonnie and Bonnie.
Get out of the car.
You hold him.
You ever shot a gun before, huh?
I just did.
Literally five minutes ago.
Can we just get my goddamn phone?
No.
I'm not making it.
Not a chauffeur.
Noted.
It's over, kid. I ain't open.
I need those tapes.
I'm not giving you those tapes.
I have the money orders. I'll trade you for one of those tapes.
I can't help you, Baby.
I shot, buddy.
Congratulations.
Then you only have every clean and dirty cop after you.
You gonna shoot me, too?
Never. You and I are a team.
Don't feed me any more lines or monsters.
Ink. It pisses me off.
It's one of Sam's favorites.
I thought it sounded familiar, you little shit.
I'm not your lucky charm anymore.
But I'm standing here asking for your help.
There's nothing I can do for you, kid.
Why should I after what you've done to me?
It's okay. Let's go.
Oh, god damn it.
Look at the two of you.
Okay. Go get your fucking tape.
It's going to take more than a cassette to get you two out of this.
Because the news is all bad.
Well, there is some good news.
The good news is you're like driving.
Because you can't take your foot off the gas for the next 20 minutes.
Then you'll be fine.
But the only good news is that you can't take your foot off the gas.
I'm sorry.
But then you're like a fucking idiot.
You're such a fucking idiot.
You're just a fucking idiot.
Because you can't take your foot off the gas for the next 25 years.
This should be enough to get you across the border.
From there, it's on you.
Don't trust anyone but each other.
And don't ever look back.
I was in love once.
Banana!
Run!
I thought...
I thought I told you to run.
Go.
I'll deal with the cops.
That's not the cops.
Here is the baby.
Your killer track.
I'm not going to let you go.
Oh, fuck.
Back! Get the back!
I'm not going to let you go.
Fuck!
We're getting out.
We're getting out?
I have to end this.
Come on out now, baby!
Romeo, Romeo!
Where for, are you?
No!
Motherfucker!
The email is out for SWAT car 3204.
It needs to be stolen by a Jason of Van Horn.
Show yourself, Fire Nation!
You fucking trials!
Hey, you okay, buddy?
Your arm and extreme knee-bathing.
Fuck!
Jesus!
Shatty!
Assistance!
Fuck you, buddy!
Shit, shit, shit!
You did good, kid.
But you took something away from me that I loved.
You know I gotta do the same.
No!
I really wish you could hear a scream.
I'm not going to let you go.
Guess you just have to watch.
What are you doing?
Getting the road.
Wiping in the music.
Is this really your mom?
Yeah.
She has a beautiful voice.
I know.
It's one reason
that I'm not going to let you go.
It's why I'm easy
I need you like Sunday morning.
Why am I worried about everybody?
The chains on the breeze.
They're too big.
Hold on a minute.
They'll be my duty to make it.
I'm not going to let you go.
I'm not happy when I try to fake it.
You don't belong in this world.
I want to be free.
How would you describe your relationship with the defendant?
We were friends.
And I think we both wanted to be more than that.
He got himself into a bad spot.
I was just trying to get him out.
I believe the defendant is of good character.
He didn't deserve what happened to him.
It was the strangest thing.
He finally drove off.
And he threw my purse right at me.
And he actually said I'm sorry.
He looked at me and he shook his head.
Like he was warning me, somehow telling me not to go inside.
He looked concerned like he was trying to save me.
He made a mistake when he was younger.
And it's haunted him ever since.
When he tried to get out, he was pressured even harder.
It was never his fault.
He's got a good heart.
Always had.
Always will.
With regard to counts one through nineteen and count twenty one.
I hear by sentence the defendant to twenty five years in the federal penitentiary.
Subject to a parole hearing after five years served.
You got a letter kid.
Hey baby.
You know it's funny.
Even though I heard it so many times in the court case.
I still can't get used to the fact that your real name is Miles.
It's a cool name though.
I can think of a lot of great milestones.
But we still have to get through all those things.
I can't wait until the day when it's just us.
Music.
And the road.
See you later baby.
All my love.
Deborah.
Music.
No, no, no, no.
Good, good, good.
Yeah, the devil behind the wheel.
Was he slow?
Richard, it means slow.
No, no, no, no.
What the hell, last morning?
You know, devil, devil, devil behind the wheel.
Richard, it means slow.
Was he slow?
No, no, no.
The devil behind the wheel.
Was he slow?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Was he slow?
No.
,, is it good?
Is it good?
Yeah, is it good?
The devil behind the wheel.
Was he slow?
No.
No, you don't sound retarded to me.
Is it good kid and devil behind the wheel.
What the hell, last morning?
You know, was he slow?
The devil behind the wheel.
Was he slow?